<resources>

    <!-- Copyright (c) Microsoft Corporation. All rights reserved. -->
    <!-- Licensed under the MIT License. -->

    <string name="app_name">ImmersiveReaderSDK</string>
    <string name="geographyTitle">Geography</string>
    <string name="geographyTextEn">The study of Earth’s landforms is called physical geography. Landforms can be mountains and valleys. They can also be glaciers, lakes or rivers. Landforms are sometimes called physical features. It is important for students to know about the physical geography of Earth. The seasons, the atmosphere and all the natural processes of Earth affect where people are able to live. Geography is one of a combination of factors that people use to decide where they want to live.The physical features of a region are often rich in resources. Within a nation, mountain ranges become natural borders for settlement areas. In the U.S., major mountain ranges are the Sierra Nevada, the Rocky Mountains, and the Appalachians.Fresh water sources also influence where people settle. People need water to drink. They also need it for washing. Throughout history, people have settled near fresh water. Living near a water source helps ensure that people have the water they need. There was an added bonus, too. Water could be used as a travel route for people and goods. Many Americans live near popular water sources, such as the Mississippi River, the Colorado River and the Great Lakes.Mountains and deserts have been settled by fewer people than the plains areas. However, they have valuable resources of their own.</string>
    <string name="geographyTextFr">L\'étude des reliefs de la Terre est appelée géographie physique. Les reliefs peuvent être des montagnes et des vallées. Il peut aussi s\'agira de glaciers, delacs ou de rivières. Les reliefs sont parfois appelés caractéristiques physiques. Il est important que les élèves connaissent la géographie physique de laTerre. Les saisons, l\'atmosphère et tous les processus naturels de la Terre affectent l\'endroit où les gens sont capables de vivre. La géographie est l\'un desfacteurs que les gens utilisent pour décider où ils veulent vivre. Les caractéristiques physiques d\'une région sont souvent riches en ressources. Àl\'intérieur d\'une nation, les chaînes de montagnes deviennent des frontières naturelles pour les zones de peuplement. Aux États-Unis, les principaleschaînes de montagnes sont la Sierra Nevada, les montagnes Rocheuses et les Appalaches.Les sources d\'eau douce influencent également l\'endroit où lesgens s\'installent. Les gens ont besoin d\'eau pour boire. Ils en ont aussi besoin pour se laver. Tout au long de l\'histoire, les gens se sont installés près del\'eau douce. Vivre près d\'une source d\'eau permet de s\'assurer que les gens ont l\'eau dont ils ont besoin. Il y avait un bonus supplémentaire, aussi. L\'eaupourrait être utilisée comme voie de voyage pour les personnes et les marchandises. Beaucoup d\'Américains vivent près des sources d\'eau populaires,telles que le fleuve Mississippi, le fleuve Colorado et les Grands Lacs.Mountains et les déserts ont été installés par moins de gens que les zones desplaines. Cependant, ils disposent de ressources précieuses.Les gens ont une réponse.</string>
    <string name="immersiveReaderButtonText">Immersive Reader</string>
</resources>
